<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>wix</title><description>wix</description><link>http://www.wix.com/demone2/public-relations-blog#!blog/c3s</link><item><title>This is the title of your first image post</title><description><![CDATA[To create your first image blog post, click here and select 'Add & Edit Posts' > All Posts > This is the title of your first image post. Great looking images make your blog posts more visually compelling for your audience, and encourage readers to keep coming back. <img src="http://static.nigiri.wixstaging.com/media/af125906a6e59a5c69576aadc4cb6679.jpg"/>]]></description><link>http://www.wix.com/demone2/public-relations-blog#!This-is-the-title-of-your-first-image-post/c16ee/1</link><guid>http://www.wix.com/demone2/public-relations-blog#!This-is-the-title-of-your-first-image-post/c16ee/1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>This is the title of your first video post</title><description><![CDATA[To create your first video blog post, click here and select 'Add & Edit Posts' > All Posts > This is the title of your first video post. Try to use videos that will engage your audience and relate to your site. Also, don’t forget to use relevant keywords in your text for SEO purposes. <img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/Y5Hk_iSs2q4/mqdefault.jpg"/>]]></description><link>http://www.wix.com/demone2/public-relations-blog#!This-is-the-title-of-your-first-video-post/c16ee/2</link><guid>http://www.wix.com/demone2/public-relations-blog#!This-is-the-title-of-your-first-video-post/c16ee/2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>This is the title of your first blog post</title><description><![CDATA[To create your first blog post, click here and select 'Add & Edit Posts' > All Posts > This is the title of your first blog post. Blogs are a great way to connect with your audience and keep them coming back. To really engage your site visitors we suggest you blog about subjects that are related to your site or business. Blogging is also really good for SEO, so we recommend including keywords that relate to your site within your posts. Good luck! ]]></description><link>http://www.wix.com/demone2/public-relations-blog#!This-is-the-title-of-your-first-blog-post/c16ee/3</link><guid>http://www.wix.com/demone2/public-relations-blog#!This-is-the-title-of-your-first-blog-post/c16ee/3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>